Guide to the Confederate States of America Collection, 1850-1876 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Volumes and Ledgers, 1861-1865, 7 volumes, 1 photocopy
  - Chimborozzo Confederate Hospital Accounts, 1863-1865 (Volume F:543)
  - Volume (Volume L:742)
  - Exemptions from Military Duty in Home Guard, 1863-1864, November 5, 1933 (Volume L:742 (photocopy))
  - Army Guard Report, Castle Pickney, Charleston, S.C., August 1864-February 1865 (Volume L:743)
  - General Order Book: 37th North Carolina Troops, October 1862-February 1863 (Volume L:746)
  - General Order Book: 37th North Carolina Troops, February 1864 (Volume L:747)
  - Roll of: Third Tennessee Regiment, 1861-1862 (Volume L:754)
  - Roll of: Edisto Rifles-Co. A, First S.C. Volunteers, 1861-1862, and Co. G, 25th S.C. Volunteers, 1862-1865, Confederate States of America (Volume S:750)